<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://nutriafresh.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://nutriafresh.com/collections/herbal-cosmetics.atom"/>
  <title>Nutria Fresh</title>
  <updated>2023-08-18T09:29:10+05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Nutria Fresh</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616180842806</id>
    <published>2023-08-18T09:29:10+05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-08-18T09:29:10+05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/products/whitening-facial-kit"/>
    <title>Whitening Facial Kit</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Nutria Fresh</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/4958/1878/files/PL_00283.jpg?v=1699550188"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Nutria Fresh<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            3600.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1">Introducing, our brand-new whitening facial kit offers you a complete whitening treatment in only a few steps! This 5-step whitening facial kit deep cleanses, exfoliates, fades dark spots, and moisturizes with a refreshing mist, leaving your skin visibly spot-less, soft, bright, and clear! A facial kit infused with Five easy steps that give tired, dull skin an instant boost of whitening.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>How to Use</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Treating yourself to a facial is one of life’s little luxuries, an at-home facial is the next best choice.<br data-mce-fragment="1">Nighttime is a great time to start. “During the day, skin is in a more protective mode, but at night, skin is more relaxed and starting repair mode, so it can readily accept extra love”</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Step 1: Whitening Face Cleanser</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">A facial cleanser is to remove dead skin cells, oil, dirt, makeup, and other pollutants from the skin.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Start by massaging the  Whitening Face cleanser on dry skin first. Then, wet your fingertips and massage them through and remove them with a wash damp cloth or sponge.<br data-mce-fragment="1">To rinse recommended to use a microfiber washcloth to provide lifting action and make sure it all comes off.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Step 2:  Whitening Face Scrub (Exfoliate)</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Exfoliating helps remove dead skin cells from the surface of your skin, and it helps make sure the rest of the products you apply are properly absorbed.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Take an appropriate amount of Amor Whitening Face Scrub and gently exfoliate your face and neck in a small circular motion to upwards direction for 5-10 minutes. Then, remove with a wash damp cloth, or sponge.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">“Someone with oilier skin can get away with exfoliating four or five times per week,”<br data-mce-fragment="1">“Someone with drier skin should exfoliate much less, about once a week.”</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Step 3: Whitening Skin Polish</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">“Present micro granules which remove surface dead skin cells and encourage new skin cells to appear, which gives an overall rejuvenated appearance to the skin.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Start by applying Amor Whitening Skin Polish from the face and go towards your neck. Avoid eye area. Then, wet your fingertips and massage it gently for 5 minutes in a circular motion and then, leaves it for 10-15 mins. Then, remove with a wash damp cloth, or sponge.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Step 4:  Whitening Face Mask</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Whitening Face Mask is one of the most gentle face masks made to remove dead cells whilst toning and lifting skin, refine skin pores, increase hydration, even akin tone, diminish fine lines.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Apply a face mask, take out a quarter-size amount spread evenly across your face and neck. Avoid your eyes. Leaves it on for 15-20 minutes, then remove with a damp cloth or, sponge.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Step 5: Whitening Face Lifting Massage Cream</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Incorporating a little massage into your facial not only feels great but also helps to increase circulation and lymphatic drainage. This can result in a dewy, de-puffed complexion. It may also reduce dullness and skin irritation.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">“If you want to use fingertips, you can or you can also use any massaging tool”</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Work from the middle out, and always go upward in motion, If you’re going to work around the eyes, you need to make sure you have enough product around them. You certainly don’t want to tug that area, since the tissue around the eyes is a lot thinner.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">“With the best Amor products and the right steps in the right order, you can give yourself a luxurious spa-quality facial at home.”</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">INGREDIENTS:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">•    Whitening face cleanser: Steric acid, sodium lorail ethail salfate. E.D.T.A, sodium ethylparaben vitamin E citreal alcohol.<br data-mce-fragment="1">•    Massage cream: Water, White soft paraffin, silicon oil, vitamin E, Cetyl alcohol, stearic acid.<br data-mce-fragment="1">•    Whitening mask: Water, titanium dioxide, stearic acid, cetyl alcohol, zinc oxide potassium hydroxide.<br data-mce-fragment="1">•    Whitening scrub: Water stearic acid, cetyl alcohol. Soft paraffin, Methyl berabin, Scrub particles, titanium dioxide.<br data-mce-fragment="1">•    Skin polish:  Water, cetyl alcohol, Glycerin, Propylene glycol sodium methylparaben.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616180842806</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="PKR">3600.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616180056374</id>
    <published>2023-08-18T09:28:22+05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-08-18T09:28:22+05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/products/hand-wash"/>
    <title>Hand Wash</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Nutria Fresh</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/4958/1878/files/handwash.webp?v=1692332904"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Nutria Fresh<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            360.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Keep your hands clean and protected with Nutria Fresh Handwash. This gentle yet effective formula is enriched with natural ingredients to remove dirt, germs, and bacteria without stripping your skin of its natural oils. Nutria Fresh Handwash leaves your hands feeling soft, smooth, and refreshed.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Benefits:</b></p>
<span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Removes dirt, germs, and bacteria</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Gentle on the skin</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Moisturizing and nourishing</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Leaves hands feeling soft, smooth, and refreshed</span><br>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1"></ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Suitable for:</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">All skin types</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Directions:</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Wet your hands, apply Nutria Fresh Handwash, lather for 20 seconds, rinse thoroughly, and dry with a clean towel for effective hand hygiene.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Ingredients:</b></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Water, surfactant, cocamidopropyl betaine, glycerin, natural extracts, and preservatives.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616180056374</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="PKR">360.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616179597622</id>
    <published>2023-08-18T09:27:53+05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-08-18T09:27:53+05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/products/hair-serum"/>
    <title>Hair Serum</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Nutria Fresh</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/4958/1878/files/hair-serum.webp?v=1692332875"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Nutria Fresh<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1530.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1">Restore your hair to its natural beauty with Nutria Fresh Onion Extract Hair Serum. This powerful formula is enriched with red onion extract, which is known for its ability to promote hair growth, reduce hair loss, and strengthen hair follicles. It also contains a blend of other natural ingredients, such as pro-vitamins and ginger extract, to nourish the scalp and leave hair soft, shiny, and manageable.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1">It is suitable for all hair types</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Benefits:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Promotes hair growth</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Reduces hair loss</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Strengthens hair follicles</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Softens and give shine</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Controls dandruff</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Reduces frizz</span><br><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;">Protects hair from damage</span><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 0.875rem;"></span><b data-mce-fragment="1">Directions:</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1">Apply a few drops of serum to damp or dry hair, focusing on the scalp and ends. Do not rinse.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Ingredients:</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1">Red onion extract, pro-vitamins, ginger extract, and other natural ingredients.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616179597622</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="PKR">1530.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616178843958</id>
    <published>2023-08-18T09:27:08+05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-08-18T09:27:08+05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/products/brightening-serum-whitening-serum"/>
    <title>Brightening Serum (Whitening Serum)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Nutria Fresh</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/4958/1878/files/weightning-serum.webp?v=1699639131"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Nutria Fresh<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1530.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1">A multitasking skin whitening serum filled with 23 high-performance ingredients effectively whitens, brightens, and corrects the appearance of skin tone for a balanced, radiant complexion.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Benefits:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">The<strong data-mce-fragment="1"> brightening serum (whitening serum)</strong> is a blend of targeted technology that takes a triple-action approach to fight the appearance of hyperpigmentation, and it also reduces the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles. The serum minimizes the appearance of dark spots and achieves a skin that’s even, radiant and glowing.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> 30 mL</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Whitens, Brightens &amp; Corrects Skin Tone</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Ends marks, acne and spots. Promotes clear face</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Safe &amp; Natural Results</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Results Appear in 10-14 Days. Use 2-4 Drops in the Morning &amp; Evening</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Reduces Melanin &amp; Dark Spots</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> Changes Skin Complexion &amp; Tone</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">→</strong> 23 High-Performance Ingredients</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">How To Apply </strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Massage 2–4 drops onto your face and neck. Use in morning and night.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616178843958</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="PKR">1530.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616178090294</id>
    <published>2023-08-18T09:26:27+05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-08-18T09:26:27+05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://nutriafresh.com/products/brightening-cream-whitening-cream"/>
    <title>Brightening Cream (Whitening Cream)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Nutria Fresh</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0818/4958/1878/files/whitning-cream-1.webp?v=1692332788"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Nutria Fresh<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2250.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1">Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream is the best fairness cream that lightens the pigmented spots and brightens skin with its pigment-lightening agents like Vitamin C (MAP), Alpha Arbutin, Licorice Extract, and Kojic Acid dipalmitate.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream in Pakistan step-up the skin brightening action with the super stable derivative of vitamin C (Magnesium Ascorbyl Phosphate), delivers constant doses of vitamin C and improves the skin barrier intact and brightened. Its skin-neutral pH lowers the chances of skin sensitivity and discomfort, thus making Nutriafresh the best fairness cream in Pakistan.</p>
<div data-mce-fragment="1" class="code-block code-block-4 ai-viewport-1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Factors like excess sun exposure, environmental factors, and pregnancy may develop darker skin patches and spots on the skin. Its size, color, and location vary, which makes it either Freckles or Melasma. Other than that, acne may also be responsible for the dark spots that appear after acne or pimple disappears. To treat bothering pigmented spots and darkened skin tone, use Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream in Pakistan. It treats common skin hyperpigmentation problems like dark skin tone, Melasma, Freckles, and Acne Marks.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">The Safriderm range offers a natural, safe, and effective skin-brightening solution. Other than Skin Brightening Cream, Antiaging Antioxidant C Cream, and Skin Brightening Face Wash complete the whole skin brightening routine.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Indications:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Nutriafresh, the best fairness cream specially formulated to reduce the appearance of pigmentations like:</p>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Dark Pigmented Skin</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Melasma/ Chloasma</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Freckles</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Acne Marks</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Uneven Skin Tones</li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>Skin Brightening Cream Ingredients</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>1. Magnesium Ascorbyl Phosphate:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Magnesium Ascorbyl Phosphate is unlike pure Vitamin C which is highly unstable, easily breakdown and causes discolorations in skin care formulations. Our Safriderm Skin Brightening Cream formula enriched with the much more stable form of Vitamin C- Magnesium Ascorbyl Phosphate (MAP) not only feeds the skin with vitamin C consistently but also plays its role as a powerful antioxidant act as a free radical hunter and increases collagen formation thus makes it the best fairness cream.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>2. Alpha Arbutin:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream comprises Alpha Arbutin, a refined form of naturally extracted “Arbutin” when applied topically inhibits the enzyme tyrosinase and hinders melanin production. Alpha Arbutin, the safest alternative to hydroquinone is enlisted in Nutriafresh Cream, making it the best fairness cream that targets the root cause and significantly lightens pigmented spots like melasma, freckles, or acne marks.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>3. Licorice Extract:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">The potent “Glabridin” within Licorice Extract actively inhibits the enzyme and so the melanin production process with which it reverses the hyperpigmented patches and spots. With the aid of Licorice extract, Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream not only fades away the dark spots but also prevents them from appearing in the future.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>4. Kojic Acid Dipalmitate:</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream is fortified with the stable and most efficacious derivative of Kojic Acid. It reduces skin pigmentation by decreasing tyrosinase activity. Because of its capacity to inhibit melanin synthesis, Kojic Acid Dipalmitate is extremely useful in lightening pigmented patches of dark skin, thus making the formulation the best fairness cream in Pakistan.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Precautions:</p>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">
<p>Store in a cool dry place (below 30°C) away from direct sunlight.</p>
</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">
<p>Keep out of reach of children.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1" class="yikes-custom-woo-tab-title yikes-custom-woo-tab-title-directions">Directions</p>
<ol data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">
<p>Apply Nutriafresh Skin Brightening Cream to the affected areas once daily at night. Massage gently into the skin until the cream is completely absorbed.</p>
</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">
<p>Use wide-spectrum sunblock  in the daytime, which protects your skin from the harmful effects of UV rays</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://nutriafresh.com/products/8616178090294</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="PKR">2250.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
